<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home-decor on DrawBuildPlay</title>
    <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/categories/home-decor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home-decor on DrawBuildPlay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.drawbuildplay.com/categories/home-decor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Outdoor Patio Lights</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outdoor-patio-lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outdoor-patio-lights/</guid>
      <description>As we gear up for the spring/summer season, I decided to add a touch of lighting to our outdoor patio/deck with some beautiful outdoor patio lights. These patio lighting are super simple to install.
One end of the lights were going to hang from the siding of the house, but I did not have anywhere to hang the other sides. So, off to Home Depot I go, and I bought some really cheap furring wood that matches the furring wood on my deck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Best DIY Natural Mosquito Repellent Plants for your yard</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/6-best-diy-natural-mosquito-repellent-plants-for-your-yard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/6-best-diy-natural-mosquito-repellent-plants-for-your-yard/</guid>
      <description>As spring rolls in, those pesky mosquitoes love to start breeding and making their home in our beautiful yards. They will target yards where there is standing water (untreated pools, creeks, poor drainage, old tires/buckets filled with water, etc). The mosquitoes will hide under the pine straw where it is moist, as well as under the leaves of trees or near their roots.
The mosquitoes tend to move in when the temperatures go above 50F, and start breeding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Outlet In Drawer</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outlet-in-drawer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outlet-in-drawer/</guid>
      <description>A must have for any bathroom or kitchen is an outlet in the drawer. It is an incredibly useful DIY to get the hair dryer, or curling/straightening iron off the counter tops, and hidden away in the drawer. But still usable. When you need it, just open the drawer, turn on the switch, and start using it. Likewise, you can install this in your kitchen and then hide your devices in a drawer while they are charging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Drawer Organizer</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-drawer-organizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-drawer-organizer/</guid>
      <description>This DIY Drawer Organizer was a spur of the moment DIY I came up with. We used to have a store bought wooden organizer a while ago which looked nice, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t sized appropriately for the drawer, and the slats had gaps below them where the silverware would sneak under (this was really annoying). Then recently, my wife went out and replaced it with a new organizer, but it was even smaller and just didn&amp;rsquo;t look good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farmhouse Ladder Shelf Decor</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/farmhouse-ladder-shelf-decor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/farmhouse-ladder-shelf-decor/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I started using Pinterest and started discovering images of other peoples homes incorporating Farmhouse elements, I have been in love. And I have sought to replicate many of these ideas in my own home.
Our latest addition to our living room has been this beautiful farmhouse ladder shelf that we purchased from Kohls.
   Farmhouse Ladder Shelf Decor    I&amp;rsquo;ve had many iterations trying to decorate this ladder shelf just right for our living room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Herb Garden Planter Box</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-herb-garden-planter-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-herb-garden-planter-box/</guid>
      <description>As the temperatures start to warm up, it&amp;rsquo;s time to start thinking about the growing season. We love to cook at our home, and a fresh batch of herbs on hand is always a life saver. Not to mention we love the smell of fresh herbs around us.
We wanted to have something close to the kitchen so that we could walk out and grab a handful of Thyme or Rosemary whenever we needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farmhouse Entryway Console Table</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/farmhouse-entryway-console-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/farmhouse-entryway-console-table/</guid>
      <description>This table was not one of my own DIY projects since it was so cheap to just go out and buy. We purchased this entry way console table from our local HomeGoods store for only $60. I probably could have DIY built it myself, but my wife saw this and wanted to get it on the spot.
This entryway console table provides a beautiful visual when our friends visit as it&amp;rsquo;s the first thing they see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Built-In Shelves using Ikea Billy Bookcase Hack</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-built-in-shelves-using-ikea-billy-bookcase-hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-built-in-shelves-using-ikea-billy-bookcase-hack/</guid>
      <description>This is probably my favorite DIY to date at home. I love how gorgeous these shelves turned out, and it only cost me a few hundred dollars.
There are a bunch of guides on Pinterest covering how to do this, but I really wanted to share ours. These shelves have seriously brightened up the office. I work remotely from home, and am constantly in Video Conferences. Having this IKEA shelf idea as a backdrop for those meetings has been a constant point of discussion, as my coworkers love how clean it looks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret DIY Tips to get a Greener Lawn</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/secret-diy-tips-to-get-a-greener-lawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/secret-diy-tips-to-get-a-greener-lawn/</guid>
      <description>As the weather is warming up, and spring is in the air, its imperative you follow the appropriate lawn maintenance schedule for your lawn. I live in the south (Atlanta to be specific), so the below tips are for the South East region. Many of our lawns have Bermuda grass, so I will be focused on this type of Bermuda grass maintenance.
There are two critical areas to focus on if you want a perfect lawn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Outdoor Landscape Lighting</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outdoor-landscape-lighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outdoor-landscape-lighting/</guid>
      <description>Plan out your Outdoor Landscape Lighting Design So, how did I DIY install my Outdoor Landscape Lighting?
Start by planning out what you want your landscape lighting design to entail.
 Where do you want up lights to light up your home? What garden features do you want to highlight? What obstacles will get in the way of wiring? Do you want down lights?  If so, do you have a way to hide the cable through the gutters/down spouts?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laundry Room Makeover</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/laundry-room-makeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/laundry-room-makeover/</guid>
      <description>Hi DIYers. Welcome to my latest post on DIY projects. This is one of the first projects I ever completed at home and inspired me to do many more since then. Our home came equipped with two locations for the laundry room. The standard one was downstairs behind the kitchen in what I consider to be a massively oversized room for a laundry. But, we also asked the builder to equip one of the closets upstairs to be a laundry room, which he happily obliged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Under Cabinet Lighting</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-under-cabinet-lighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-under-cabinet-lighting/</guid>
      <description>One of the things we wanted to do when we built our home was to have under cabinet lighting in our kitchen. Getting this from our builder was going to be $200 per light, and with three sections in our kitchen this would have easily cost us $600 - $1000 depending on how much we got.
After researching some ideas, we decided to install wired puck lights ourselves afterwards. I had the builder install power outlets above the cabinets, connected to a wall switch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>