<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>smart-home on DrawBuildPlay</title>
    <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/categories/smart-home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in smart-home on DrawBuildPlay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.drawbuildplay.com/categories/smart-home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Outdoor Patio Lights</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outdoor-patio-lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outdoor-patio-lights/</guid>
      <description>As we gear up for the spring/summer season, I decided to add a touch of lighting to our outdoor patio/deck with some beautiful outdoor patio lights. These patio lighting are super simple to install.
One end of the lights were going to hang from the siding of the house, but I did not have anywhere to hang the other sides. So, off to Home Depot I go, and I bought some really cheap furring wood that matches the furring wood on my deck.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Smart Home Tech for your home</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/10-best-smart-home-tech-for-your-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/10-best-smart-home-tech-for-your-home/</guid>
      <description>As we start to jump into tech gadgets for the home, one of the first decisions we need to make is if we want to take advantage of a specific ecosystem (Apple vs Google vs Amazon), or try to keep our options open as the major tech companies fight it over. My preference has been to try to stay as universal as possible, while choosing the best tech out there for its purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Outlet In Drawer</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outlet-in-drawer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-outlet-in-drawer/</guid>
      <description>A must have for any bathroom or kitchen is an outlet in the drawer. It is an incredibly useful DIY to get the hair dryer, or curling/straightening iron off the counter tops, and hidden away in the drawer. But still usable. When you need it, just open the drawer, turn on the switch, and start using it. Likewise, you can install this in your kitchen and then hide your devices in a drawer while they are charging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to DIY install a USB outlet</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/how-to-diy-install-a-usb-outlet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/how-to-diy-install-a-usb-outlet/</guid>
      <description>USB Outlets is really a must have in any home these days. With all of our devices - from iPhones and Androids, to iPads and other tablets, it seems like we are always charging something.
But, when we are charging, I hate having that charging brick sticking out of the wall all the time. I am also always hunting around for a wire, or free outlet in a convenient spot so that I can charge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Home Security Ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-home-security-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-home-security-ideas/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s 2019 and many of you may still be paying traditional alarm providers for alarm monitoring. But did you know there are many easy DIY options that are in many ways better and cheaper than what you are paying them?
First, let&amp;rsquo;s break down the typical cost.
Basic Monitoring Plans A basic alarm monitoring package (2 door sensors, 1 basic keypad, and 1 motion sensor) is going to typically set you back $30/mo on a 3 year term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY How To Save your New Car From Little Muddy Kicking Feet</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-how-to-save-your-new-car-from-little-muddy-kicking-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/diy-how-to-save-your-new-car-from-little-muddy-kicking-feet/</guid>
      <description>So a few months ago I purchased a new Tesla Model 3. It&amp;rsquo;s my dream car and I am totally in love with it. We made this our main car, which meant with two kids we have two car seats in the back.
Anyone with kids in will know that for some reason they have to kick the seats in front of them. It&amp;rsquo;s all that energy they have I guess where they can&amp;rsquo;t just sit still.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch TV for Free without cable</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/watch-tv-for-free-without-cable/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/watch-tv-for-free-without-cable/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in my previous blog post on [Part One - How to stop paying for your landline](https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/how-to-cut-the-cord-stop-paying-for-your-landline/), most people pay between $100 and $250 each month to their cable providers. They are paying for Internet, Phone, and TV. My last post showed how you can save at least $20 per month by not paying your cable company for a phone line. Now for the bigger savings. Lets save some money by watching TV for free without cable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Cut the Cord - Stop paying for your landline</title>
      <link>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/how-to-cut-the-cord-stop-paying-for-your-landline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.drawbuildplay.com/blog/how-to-cut-the-cord-stop-paying-for-your-landline/</guid>
      <description>Many homes are still subscribed to cable. Many are still paying for bundled services like Phone, Internet, and TV. Often, these nasty cable bills are around $200 per month.
Now, what if I told you you didnt need to pay for phone or TV. You can get internet service in most places for between $30 - $100 depending on how fast broadband speeds you want. I currently pay AT&amp;amp;T for their Gigabit Fiber network $70/month.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>